<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home Page on Social Science Exam project</title><link>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/</link><description>Recent content in Home Page on Social Science Exam project</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data description</title><link>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/data-description/</guid><description>The data of this analysis are reviews of Amazon fine food products as well as some metadata for the products in the reviews. For the reviews themselves we have some
The 1139892 reviews of 39320 products are loaded into a pandas dataframe. Each row in the dataframe corresponds to a review and each column is a variable for the review. Below, we&amp;rsquo;ve included a snippet of the review dataframe.
The header in each column explains the variables of the review in each row.</description></item><item><title>Network analysis</title><link>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/network-analysis/</guid><description>In the network analysis we connect products that have common users having reviewed them. So if two arbitrary products have been reviewed by the same user they are connected in the graph.
We will use different analytical tools to see the structure of the network.
Since the edges of the graph are users who reviewed the same product, we expect to see some groupings of users who review similar products.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nullerh.github.io/02467_group4/text-analysis/</guid><description>First and foremost clean and tokenize the review texts. Everything is lowercased, stemmed, stopwords and hyperlinks are removed, as well as backslash commands that may appear.
Since the result of the text analysis is heavily dependent on the preprocessing we actually performed the whole analysis and then went back and changed the preprocessing, realizing that we should use stemming, remove some irrelevant words, which made the text analysis a recursive proces.</description></item></channel></rss>