<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>What is this project about? on Amazon fine food reviews</title><link>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/</link><description>Recent content in What is this project about? on Amazon fine food reviews</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data description</title><link>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/data-description/</guid><description>The data of this analysis are reviews of Amazon fine food products as well as some metadata for the products in the reviews. For the reviews themselves we have some
The 1.1 millions reviews are loaded into a pandas dataframe. Note that only products and users that have at least 5 reviews are in the dataset. Each row in the dataframe corresponds to a review and each column is a variable for the review.</description></item><item><title>Network analysis</title><link>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/network-analysis/</guid><description>In the network analysis we connect products that have 15 common products also viewed or purchased. So if two arbitrary products have been viewed or purchased with at least 15 of the same other products they are connected in the graph.
We will use different analytical tools to see the structure of the network.
We expect to see some groupings products based on the hypothesis that users who view or buy e.</description></item><item><title>Text analysis</title><link>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eortvald.github.io/02467_group4/text-analysis/</guid><description>First and foremost clean and tokenize the review texts. Everything is lowercased, stemmed, stopwords and hyperlinks are removed, as well as backslash commands that may appear.
We use the documents of the products to carry out a sentiment analysis and cross-reference this to the review score, where we expect to see some correlation between the review score and sentiment score of the product reviews.
In order to get the sentiment score of the reviews we use the Hedonometer sentiment score and take the mean over the document for each product which yields a general sentiment of a product.</description></item></channel></rss>